const data = [
  {
    question: " What\'s the top reason investors choose an ESG fund?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "They hear about values-driven investing from their friends",
      "They see it mentioned on social media",
      'They learn about ESG funds in college'
    ],
    correctAnswer:  "Their financial professional suggests it",
  },
  {
    question: "  In 2020, what portion of sustainable equity funds performed better than their conventional peers?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "52%",
      "36%",
      "20%"
    ],
    correctAnswer:  "75%",
  },

  {
    question:
      "How can ESG factors become nancially material to a company?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "The media calls out business practices that are harming society",
      "An industry begins to regulate itself and establish norms that harmful practices aren't acceptable",
      "Innovation transforms an industry, and as a result, ESG factors can no longer be ignored",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of the above"
  },
 
  {
    question: "What ESG investing approach accounted for $17.5 trillion in assets in 2018?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Norms-based screening", 
       "Negative screening",
       "Best-in-class investing"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "ESG integration",
  },
  {
    question: "  In an average ESG dataset from a third-party data provider like Bloomberg or MSCI, how many companies are research covered?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "More than 2,000", 
      "More than 5,000", 
      "More than 17,000"],
    correctAnswer: "More than 11,000",
  },
  {
    question: "Which investor might prefer an impact investing approach?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Someone who doesn't care about the financial return on their investments",
      " Someone who wants to make sure their investments don't support companies that act against their values",
      "Someone who wants to evaluate ESG risks and opportunities when selecting investments"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Someone who wants to use their assets to create positive change"
  },
  {
    question: "  What's one reason why stronger ESG regulation should be considered?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Shareholders are pressuring companies to disclose ESG risks, and it’s important to ensure companies aren't revealing trade secrets",
      "While investors are paying more attention to ESG factors, it’s also important for them not to lose sight of financial considerations",
    ],
    correctAnswer:  "Investors recognize the importance of ESG data and disclosures, and they should have the information needed to make good decisions"
  },
{
  question : "Which of these investment approaches would be most suitable for an investor who wants to ensure that their personal, social and moral views direct the investment decisions?",
  incorrectAnswers: [

  "Thematic investing.",
  "Impact investing.",
  "Responsible investing."],
    correctAnswer:  "Ethical investing.",
},

 {question : "Which UK body is responsible for issuing the Stewardship Code?",
 incorrectAnswers: [ "The Financial Conduct Authority (FCA).",
 "The Financial Policy Committee (FPC).",
  "The Financial Ombudsman Service (FOS).",
 ],
    correctAnswer:  "The Financial Reporting Council (FRC).",
},
{
  question : "A Sovereign Wealth Fund selecting an investment manager with an ESG strategy is likely to focus more on the manager's approach to:",
 incorrectAnswers: [
   "Integrating MSCI data while ESG scoring the portfolio.",
 "Liquidity of the portfolio and short-term performance.",
 "ESG engagement and stewardship.",
 ],
    correctAnswer:  "Quantitative analysis of portfolio attribution vs. the benchmark."
},
{
  question : "Which of these least reflects how qualitative ESG data is used in company analysis?",
 incorrectAnswers: [ 
   "To adjust a valuation.",
  "To modify a financial model.",
  "To determine the value at risk for the company."],
  correctAnswer:  "To add an opinion to an investment thesis.",
 },
 {
  question : "Adjusting the Discounted Cash Flow when integrating ESG into traditional financial analysis is:",
 incorrectAnswers: [
  "Valid at the level of company, sector or country.",
 "Valid only at the level of company.",
  "Not valid at sector level."],
  correctAnswer: "Not valid at country level.",
 },
  {
 question : "Which action would be undertaken first by an investor wanting to follow an engagement strategy with a company in a cost effective way?",
 incorrectAnswers: [  "Defining the scope of engagement and prioritising engagement activities.",
  "Developing a clear process which articulates realistic goals.",
  "Framing the engagement topic into a broader strategy discussion."
],
correctAnswer:  "Adapting the engagement process to the local context.",
  },
  {
  question : "Which comment best reflects the inclusion of 'bad actor' companies which have poor ESG scores in ESG mutual funds?",
  incorrectAnswers: [ "Bad actors are never included.",
   "Bad actors are rarely included.",
  "Bad actors will always be included."],
  correctAnswer:    "Bad actors are often included.",
  },
  {
 question : "What is an indirect environmental impact of a paper company cutting trees and transporting them to its production plant?",
  incorrectAnswers: [ "Carbon emissions from the haulage lorries.",
  "A natural regulator of carbon dioxide is destroyed,",
  "Deforestation.",
 ],
  correctAnswer:  "Local species are disturbed."
  },
{question :  "Which of the following approaches is most likely to result in an analyst aggregating numeric variables into an ESG score?",
  incorrectAnswers: [
  "Fundamental analysis.",
  "Stock picking.",
  "Quantitative modelling."],
  correctAnswer:  "Company specific research.",
} ,
  {
 question : "What impact will a positive ESG rating have on a company's cost of capital?",
  incorrectAnswers: [ "lower cost of capital.",
  ],
  correctAnswer: "No change to the cost of capital."
  },
  {
 question : "Which of the following sectors have the greatest risk of increased insurance costs due to physical climate change?",
  incorrectAnswers: [ 
    "Construction and materials.",
  "Food and beverage.",
  ],
  correctAnswer: "Travel and leisure"
  }
]
export default data;
